{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1144","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #785","address":"16100 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221","owner":"Falcon Holdings, LLC","licenseNumber":"035226","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.14036,42.40998","geojson":{"id":"1144","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.140361582,42.40998068]},"properties":{"name":"Church's Fried Chicken #785","owner":"Falcon Holdings, LLC","address":"16100 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"035226","establishmentid":"1144","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/24/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1023","name":"U Of D Coney Island #1","address":"16126 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5164","name":"Burger King #21688","address":"16245 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1556","name":"Uptown Bar B Que","address":"15700 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48238"},{"establishmentid":"880","name":"U of Detroit Mercy- Calihan Hall","address":"4001 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4438","name":"U of Detroit Mercy-Tommy's Smoothies","address":"4001 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4143","name":"U of Detroit Mercy-Library Cafe","address":"4001 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"4413","name":"U of Detroit Mercy-Subway","address":"4001 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1577","name":"U of Detroit Mercy-Student Cafe/Poblanos","address":"4001 W McNichols Rd","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"5306","name":"Livernois Ocean Delight Inc","address":"16817 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"},{"establishmentid":"1674","name":"Nicky D's Coney Island","address":"16953 Livernois Ave","zipcode":"48221"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"47659","inspectionDate":"2019-05-09T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"45478","inspectionDate":"2019-03-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-102.11","violationDescription":"The PERSON IN CHARGE shall demonstrate this knowledge by compliance with this Code, by being a certified FOOD protection manager who has shown proficiency of required information through passing a test that is part of an ACCREDITED PROGRAM, or by responding correctly to the inspector's questions as they relate to the specific FOOD operation. (Pf)","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Does not demonstrate required knowledge","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Missing","subProblem":"","location":"PERSON IN CHARGE","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide manufacture lable "},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2019-03-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"43307","inspectionDate":"2018-08-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"41369","inspectionDate":"2018-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."}]},{"inspectionid":"40188","inspectionDate":"2017-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"39385","inspectionDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"3-303.12","violationDescription":"PACKAGED FOOD may not be stored in direct contact with ice or water,  except as allowed by LAW.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Packaged food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored","subProblem":"In direct contact with ice","location":"ICE BIN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discontinue use."}]},{"inspectionid":"37275","inspectionDate":"2016-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"36701","inspectionDate":"2016-10-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-05-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1144"}}